Guide to the Branford College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1958-2013 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Branford College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1958-2013 maintained by the dean
1954-2013
RU 254
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
121.33
(132 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Branford College, Yale University.
Branford College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-D-1 (YRG 13-D-1), Records of the dean of Branford College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Branford College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically by class year.
College students; Branford College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1958, 1954-1958; Series I
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2034
  - Class of 1958 student Pictures (Box 1)
- Student records for the Class of 1959, 1955-1959; Series II
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
  - Class of 1959 photographs, 1955-1959 (Box 1)
  - 1959 Yale Commencement Program (Box 1)
  - Questionnaires (Box 1)
- Student records for the Class of 1960, 1956-1960; Series III
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Pictures for the Class of 1960, 1956-1960 (Box 2)
  - Questionaires, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Ex-students, 1956-1960 (Box 3)
- Student records for the Class of 1961, 1957-1961; Series IV
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - Questionnaires (1961), 1957-1961 (Box 3)
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1962, Series V
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  - Photos, 1958-1962 (Box 4)
- Student records for the Class of 1963, 1959-1963; Series VI
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - Activities Reports (1963), 1959-1963 (Box 5)
  - Ex-students, 1959-1963
- Student records for the Class of 1964, 1960-1964; Series VII
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1965, 1961-1965; Series VIII
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1966, 1962-1966; Series IX
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1967, 1963-1967; Series X
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1968, 1964-1968; Series XI
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
- Student records for the Class of 1969, 1965-1969; Series XII
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
- Student records for the Class of 1970, 1966-1970; Series XIII
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
- Student records for the Class of 1971, 1967-1971; Series XIV
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2047
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1972, 1968-1972; Series XV
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2048
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1973, 1969-1973; Series XVI
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2049
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1974, 1970-1974; Series XVII
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
- Student records for the Class of 1975, 1971-1975; Series XVIII
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
  - Recommendation Folders A-C, 1971-1975 (Box 31)
  - Recommendation Folders D-J, 1971-1975 (Box 31)
  - Recommendation Folders K-M, 1971-1975 (Box 31)
  - Recommendation Folders P-Z, 1971-1975 (Box 31)
- Student records for the Class of 1976, 1972-1976; Series XIX
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1977, Series XX
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  - Class of 1977 File, 1972-1976 (Box 34)
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1978, 1974-1978; Series XXI
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
- Student records for the Class of 1975-1978 (impounded), 1971-1978; Accession 1975-A-002; 3.75; (6 boxes)
  Restricted until January 1, 2054.
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
- Student records for the Class of 1979, Accession 1984-A-009
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
- Student records for the Class of 1980, Accession 1985-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
- Student records for the Class of 1981, Accession 1987-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1982, Accession 1988-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
- Student records for the Class of 1983, Accession 1991-A-118
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Classes of 1984-1985, Accession 1992-A-077
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - 1984
  - 1985
    - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1986, Accession 1993-A-001
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1987, Accession 1993-A-002
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Withdrawals (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Student records for the Class of 1988, Accession 1993-A-094
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1989, Accession 1997-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1990, Accession 1997-A-094
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1991, Accession 2000-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1992, Accession 2001-A-001
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1993, Accession 2001-A-084
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
- Student records for the Class of 1994, Accession 2001-A-098
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1995, Accession 2001-A-122
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1996, Accession 2004-A-191
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 1997, Accession 2005-A-145
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1998, Accession 2007-A-061
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1999, Accession 2008-A-039
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075]
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2000, 1995-2001; Accession 2008-A-188
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - WITHDRAWALS
- Student records for the Classes of 2001-2003, 1997-2003; Accession 2010-A-091
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2079
  - CLASS OF 2001
  - Class of 2002
  - Class of 2003
- Student records for the Classes of 2004-2009, Accession 2014-A-069
  Restricted until January 1, 2084
- Student records for the Classes of 2010 through 2013, 2006-2013; Accession 2018-A-018
  Restricted until January 1, 2089
  - Class of 2010
  - Class of 2011
  - Class of 2012
  - Class of 2013